[{"answer": "yeah, what happened", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Sue my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "That is just shameless, I don't know, There's n", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It's wrong, it's rude, and it'", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Sue my friend? Ah, alright, send her in.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah, so", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You know last time you had me throwin' a rye bread up three floors to you, now you want me to go up to the that place, take flyers off your car, where does it end?!", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Sue my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I got your message, how's the shoulder", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, no. Not the left arm", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Then what happened", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No top? She didn't have a top on", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How 'bout a 'good morning'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Good morning to you, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't know, so the woman was walking around in a bra, I mean it's no big deal. You're still drivin'. You should have been watching the road", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't think my attitude has changed", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "And what about yooou?!? Tryin' to bilk an innocent bystander out of a family fortune, built on sweat and toil, manufacturing quality O'Henry candy bars, for honest, har", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You're just out for money", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yesss", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I can't believe it, he was so young. How could this have happened", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, he'd been logging some pretty heavy hours, first one in in the morning, last one to leave at night. That kid was a human dynamo", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You are Mr. and Mrs. my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Dead", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "My car is a little crumpled?!", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well you gotta call your parents", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Aren't you gonna tell your parents you're still alive", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What was you golf score, the last round you played...before you shoulder was injured", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Caddy.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend, three under par...That's what the professionals shoot, isn't it", "qsentId": 30}]